把阿憨的盘子偷回家
Stealing Han's dishes
我们的就不用洗了  这做法太聪明了
so we don't have to clean ours at home is genius.
同时也有点小可悲
And a little sad.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
这是早上来大姨妈后
This is the greatest thing that's happened to me
发生在我身上最棒的事情了
Since I got my period this morning.
麦克斯  卡洛琳  你们居然偷我的盘子
Max, Caroline, you're stealing my dishes?
靠  我还以为这么高你会看不见呢
Damn it, I didn't think you could see up this high.
我也以为这么低贱的事你们干不出来呢
And I didn't think you could sink this low.
住手  我们已经用"我是个服务员"的把戏
Okay, stop, you're already robbing me blind
骗走我很多钱了
with your "I'm a waitress" scam.
抱歉嘛  但最近我们家里有点脏乱
Sorry, but things have gotten kind of messy at home.
昨天我得洗第二次澡
Yesterday, I had to take a shower
才洗干净我第一次洗澡时弄脏的
to shower off the shower I took.
你们俩应该请个清洁工
You two should get a cleaning lady.
我有花钱请个妞来帮我打扫公寓
I have a woman I pay to clean my apartment.
她收费挺高的  但如果不包括上床的话
She is expensive, but she may charge you less
她可能会少收一点
if you don't also have sex on her.
我帮你们问问看吧
I'll look into it.
我奶奶以前打扫房子都不要钱
My grandmother cleaned the house free of charge.
当然不是她不要  而是没人给
Of course she didn't have a say in the matter.
我们问问苏菲把  她有个清洁公司
Let's just ask Sophie. She has a cleaning service.
我们必须得采取行动了
We have to do something.
昨天我看见一只蟑螂爬出了我们的公寓
Yesterday, I saw a roach walk out of our apartment.
听着
Look.
对于此事  我的回答就跟有人曾问我
I'm gonna tell you what I told that guy
能否用我的屁股帮他走私鸦片时一样
who asked me to use my butt to smuggle opium.
当然好啦
I'll do it!
快准备好  麦克斯
Be ready, Max.
等清洁工一到  我们就得走啦
We have to leave as soon as the cleaning lady gets here.
这是屋主不成文的规矩
It's housekeeper etiquette.
我以前会去健身馆上单车课  然后跟朋友吃午饭
In my old life, I go to spin class and lunch with friends,
但现在我们只能去外面
but you and I will just go outside
看那个刚从监狱放出来的家伙
and watch the guy who just got out of jail
在灯柱上做引体向上
do pull-ups on the light post.
卡尔文出狱了吗
Calvin's out?
我才不会走
I'm not gonna leave.
我要看着她收拾我弄的烂摊子
I want to watch her clean up my mess.
没错  宝贝
Yeah, baby.
我等了一辈子  终于等来个仆人了
I've waited my whole life to have a servant.
开始那几周  我以为你会成为我的仆人
I thought you were gonna be it for the first few weeks
但后来我发现你什么都不会做
and then I realized you can't do anything.
即使苏菲给我们打了个折
And even though Sophie gave us a discount,
那女仆还是得称我为"殿下"[高]
the maid still has to call me "Your highness."
主要因为我现在抽大麻嗨"高"了
Mostly because I'm pretty "highness" right now.
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
我来啦
Here I am.
"苏菲的选择清洁公司"的苏菲
Sophie from Sophie's choice cleaning service.
这位是你们的清洁工  宝琳娜
Meet your cleaning lady Paulina.
宝琳娜  这两位是屋主
Paulina, meet the girls.
她也想握手  但她只有一条胳膊
She'd shake hands, but she only has one arm.
苏菲  她能听到你说话
Sophie, she can hear you.
那又怎么样  我知道我少了条胳膊
So what? I know I'm missing arm.
这又不是什么新闻
It's not news.
她不就是丢了条胳膊嘛
So she lost an arm.
我的金耳环还丢在垃圾处理机了呢
I lost my gold earring down the garbage disposal
但我不敢伸手去拿
but I was too afraid to reach into it
因为  你们懂的
Because, well, yeah.
别担心
Don't worry.
打扫起来  我一条胳膊顶三条用
I have one arm but I clean like I have three.
我去补补妆  然后就开始干活
I put on more makeup, then I start.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
我真不知道请清洁工时
I didn't realize when I ordered a cleaning lady
还得特地说明我要两只手都能干活的
I had to specify I wanted one with two arms.
两条胳膊的你请不起
You can't afford two arms.
你说了要便宜点
You said you wanted a good price.
所以一条胳膊  一半价格
Half the arms, half the price.
所以她那条胳膊才没的吧  苏菲
Is that how she lost the arm, Sophie?
你为了给我们打折  所以打折了她的胳膊
You cut it off so we could get a discount?
是啊  没错
Oh, yeah, sure.
我把她的胳膊锯下来  只为了给你们省10块钱
Yeah, I sawed off her arm so I could save you 10 bucks.
我先从卧室开始
I start in bedroom.
慢着  在开工前问你个问题
Wait, before you do, one question.
你的胳膊怎么没的  像詹姆斯·弗兰科那样吗
How'd you lose it? James Franco situation?
为了逃命必须把胳膊割断吗
You had to cut it off to get loose?
沉默等于默认
You're not saying no.
算了吧  还是不要深究了
Oh, you know what, let's not go there.
都发生了  就让它过去吧
You know, it happened, it was in the past.
我被困在一辆大卡车下
I was trapped under this big truck.
知道啦
We get it.
是我从你胳膊上碾了过去
I drove over your arm.
别费力气去卧室翻我的好首饰了
Hey, don't even bother looking for my good jewelry in there
因为我已经全部戴在身上了
because I'm already wearing all of it.
真是羡慕死我了  我居然没有胳膊
Oh, I'm jealous I don't have arm
戴这种廉价的首饰
to wear cheap jewelry.
麦克斯  我觉得她很可怜
Max, I feel bad for her.
瞧  这就是我们要离开的原因
See? This is why you leave.
以防清洁工妆太浓
In case they show up with too much makeup
而胳膊太少
and not enough arms.
放心  她很坚强
Relax, she's tough.
让我想起年轻的我
Reminds me of a young me.
也就是说我要去把药藏起来  以防她找到
Which means I better go hide my pills from her.
麦克斯  别走  我怕她
Max, don't leave, she scares me.
拜托  她没有手[武器]好吗
Oh, come on, she's armless.
一切顺利吗  需要帮忙吗
Everything okay? You need any help?
我在打扫这行能有今天  可不是靠别人帮忙的
I didn't get this far in this business by taking help.
帮帮我  你没看见我只有一条胳膊
Help me! Can't you see I got one arm?
没问题
Not gonna be a problem.
我偶尔也会帮我的女仆
I would occasionally help my maid--
你不想听是吧
You're not interested.
抬起来
Lift!
使劲  小弱鸡  抬起来
Lift, weak girl. Lift.
麦克斯  过来  我们要把你的床垫抬起来
Max, come here. We need help lifting your mattress.
你能帮我们一把吗
Can you give us a hand?
不  别抬  放下来
No! Leave it alone! Leave it alone!
不要把床垫抬起来
Don't lift up the mattress!
黄书
Ah, porno.
你的思想跟你的公寓一样脏
Your mind is as dirty as your apartment!
是黄书怎么样  有什么大不了的
Yes, it's porn. So what? What's the big deal?
那不过是人类正常的肉体
It's just the body in its natural form,
在摩托车上叉开腿卖骚而已
spread-eagle on a motorcycle.
为什么大部分人看着都像80年代的啊
Why is so much of it from the 80's?
我喜欢小胡子  可以了吗
I like mustaches, okay?
而且我还有另一项任务  就是寻找我的生父
And it's multitasking. I'm looking for my father.
别看了  不许看了
Stop looking. Stop looking right now.
你干嘛突然不好意思啊
Why are you suddenly embarrassed?
你的主页就是"色情之家"
Porn Hub is your homepage.
这是烘焙学校的宣传册吗
Hey, is this a brochure for pastry school?
你为什么要把烘焙学校的宣传册藏起来
Why are you hiding a pastry school brochure?
你妹才藏烘焙学校的宣传册呢
Your face is a pastry school brochure!
麦克斯  你对烘焙学校感兴趣很好啊
Max, it's great you're interested in pastry school.
为什么你要不好意思呢
I don't know why you're embarrassed.
你妹才不好意思呢
Your face is embarrassed!
别这样嘛  我真的觉得
Come on, I really think that this is
我们该好好谈谈这事
something we should talk about.
你妹才要跟你谈呢
Your face is something we should talk about!
你把吓人的妞气跑了
You made the scary one mad.
真是愚蠢之极啊
That was dumb move.
你妹才愚蠢之极呢
Your face was a dumb move!
麦克斯
Max?
麦克斯  你冲出去就再也没有回来
Max, you never came home after you stormed out,
所以我把你的制服带来了
so I brought you your uniform.
麦克斯
Max?
老娘现在住这里了
I live here now.
我的新室友  扫把和拖把
My new roommates, the broom and the mop,
不会鬼鬼祟祟乱翻我的东西
don't sneak around looking at my stuff.
这里什么都有
I got everything I need.
威士忌  牙刷  牙膏
Whiskey, toothbrush, toothpaste.
或许你的扫把室友
Well, maybe your new broommate
依你现在的状态看  离狂吐还有不到一小时
Which, from the looks of it, will be in about an hour.
麦克斯  我们真的谈谈这本宣传册
Max, we really need to talk about this brochure.
就因为我有一本烘焙学校的宣传册
Look, just because I have a pastry school brochure
并不意味着我真的想去
doesn't mean I'm actually gonna go to pastry school.
就像我有很多黄书
Just like having those porn magazines
也不意味着我会真的骑着一只老虎
doesn't mean I'm actually gonna ride around on a tiger
跟水手们做一些很黄很暴力的行为  大概不会吧
performing unspeakable acts with sailors, probably.
烘焙学校就跟黄书一样
Pastry school is the same as porn.
不过是愚蠢意淫而已
It's just a dumb fantasy.
烘焙学校才不像黄书
Pastry school is not like porn.
这本宣传册上完全没有提及"女女合欢"羊角面包
There is nothing in this brochure about a girl-on-girl croissant
这牙膏真不错
That's good toothpaste.
拜托别拿酒刷牙了
Please stop brushing your teeth.
我们晚点还要上班呢
We have a shift to do later.
曼哈顿的烘培学校
Okay, the Manhattan school of pastry--
你妹才是曼哈顿的烘培学校
Your face is the Manhattan school of pastry.
我也希望是
You know it isn't.
麦克斯  你真的可以去上
Max, you could go here for real.
学费一年才三千  虽然很多  但上得起
Tuition is only $3,000 a year. A lot, but doable.
虽然很多  但上得起
A lot but doable?
我们说的是烘焙学校  还是快打烊时使劲点餐的胖子
Are we talking about pastry school or fat guy at last call?
我们到了  麦克斯  你的梦想从现在开始
Here we are, Max. Your dream starts now.
我要变成黑色美人鱼了吗
What, the one where I'm a black mermaid?
放松点行吗
Would you relax?
我们就四处看看  然后拿份申请表
We're just gonna look around and get an application.
如果你来这学习  就能用所有这些高档的设备
See all that gorgeous equipment you get to use if you went here?
你终于要有一个真正的搅拌碗了
Finally you'd have a mixing bowl
而不是中间挖空的西瓜
that's not a hollowed-out watermelon.
能救救我吗
Can you help me?
我是被她挟持的人质
She's holding me against my will.
她开玩笑呢
She's kidding.
小姑娘  如果你一直这样
If you keep this up, young lady,
别想有冰淇淋吃
you are not getting ice cream after.
过来  办公室在这
Come on, here's the office.
随便啦  完事了没啊
Whatever. Are we almost done here?
我等下要出庭受审呢
I got a court date later.
你好
Hi.
我不确定我们是否来对地方了
I'm not sure we're in the right place.
我们仨都没来对吗
Are any of us really?
我们想要份申请表  你可以帮个忙吗
We'd like an application. Could you help us?
天啊  希望可以
Oh, god, I hope so.
我没想到第一天回来  就会碰到
I wasn't expecting something this high-pressure
这么高强度的工作
my first day back.
我之前在精神病院留院观察了一段时间
Let's just say I've been under observation at the nuthouse.
好的  申请表是吧
Okay, application.
是麦克斯要的
It's for Max, here.
你们的宣传册给她留下深刻的印象
She was very impressed by your brochure.
烘焙学校  令人兴奋  对吧
Oh, pastry school. Exciting, right?
我曾是一位大厨  但后来就不是了
I was a chef here once. And then I wasn't.
瞧  找到申请表了
Oh, look. Found the application.
真的没想到我能处理好这件事
Really didn't think I was gonna be able to handle that.
碧碧  如果你...
Bebe, if you--
早安[法语]  早上好
Bonjour. Good morning.
尼古拉斯主厨  这两位姑娘是来拿申请表的
Chef Nicolas, these girls are here for an application.
别担心  我处理好了
Don't worry, I handled it.
差点失败  但我成功了
Almost didn't, then I did.
干得好  碧碧
Nice work, Bebe.
我好像听出来有法国口音哦  是吗
Oh, do I detect a French accent? Oui?
天啊  我看不下眼了
Oh, my god, I can't watch.
其实我是法国人  我是主厨尼古拉斯·圣克劳
French, indeed. I'm chef Nicolas Saintcroix,
校长兼厨师长  欢迎你们
Owner and head chef. Bienvenue.
我是卡洛琳·钱宁
Caroline Channing.
你丢脸丢完了吗
Is it over yet?
这是麦克斯  是她要申请你们学校
This is Max. The application's for her.
你好  法国佬  你吃蜗牛吗
'Sup, Frenchie? You eat snails?
貌似碧碧忘了给你们第二页了
It looks like bebe forgot the second page.
天啊  忘了第二页  这可不好
Oh, boy, forgot the second page. That's not good.
我以为我能处理好  但还是失败了
I thought I handled it. Didn't handle it.
的确是好方法
That's good stuff.
她曾经非常优秀
She was quite brilliant.
但后来就不优秀了
Then she wasn't.
给  把这表填了
Here. Fill that out.
下一步就是烘焙测试
And the next step is the pastry exam.
申请者要做一个经典的水果塔
Applicants will have to make a classic tart,
明天拿给我尝尝
bring them in tomorrow for me to taste,
然后再决定录用与否  可以吗
and we will go from there. Sound good?
随便啦  或许我会考虑下
Whatever. Maybe I'll think about it.
好吧  或许你会
Okay, well, maybe you will.
很高兴见到你们俩
Nice meeting you both.
希望明天能看见你哦  大厨
Hope to see you tomorrow, chef.
他刚叫我大厨
He called me chef!
-太棒了  咱们去买冰淇淋吧  -不行
- Yay! Let's go get ice cream! - No!
你应该开始做水果塔
You should get started on that tart.
明天就要交了
It's due tomorrow.
我有大把时间呢
I got plenty of time.
再说了  有压力才会有动力
Besides, pressure ups my game.
当有人拿枪指着我的头时  我会做得更好
I perform my best when there's a gun to my head.
不信问我以前的男朋友
Ask any of my ex-boyfriends.
我可不会这么对待我的考试[检查]
This is so not how I prepare for tests.
就连子宫颈抹片检查  我都得先研究三周
I studied three weeks for a pap smear.
别担心  我能行
Don't worry, I got this.
水果塔就是往饼干上放点布丁  对吧
A tart's just like a cookie with some pudding on it, right?
麦克斯  这里是什么情况
Max, what is going on in here?
原来水果塔不止往饼干上放点布丁那么简单
Turns out a tart's more than a cookie with some pudding on it!
你都在里面六小时了  你说过你能行的
You've been in here six hours. You said you had this.
我以为我能行  但原来我不行
I thought I had this! Turns out I don't!
我甚至连塔皮都没做出来
I haven't even finished a shell.
我都不知道到底有没有塔皮  你觉得有吗
I didn't know there was a shell. Did you know there was a shell?
水果塔当然有塔皮啦
Everybody knows there's a shell!
你的脑子怎么了  也没皮了吗
What the shell is wrong with you?
我是一个不会做水果塔的贱人[tart一词多义]
I'm a tart who can't make a tart!
到现在你早应该做出九个塔皮了
You could've made nine shells by now.
我做了啊  它们都在这呢  看
I did. They're all in here. Look.
这就是"死亡塔皮"
It's like Shell-Mageddon!
不管了  反正这个等下也要进垃圾桶
Oh, screw it. This one's gonna be there in a minute.
还不如先扔进去呢
Let's just get it over with.
不  你不能这样做  来
No, you can do this. Here. Here.
这个看起来还不错
This still looks ready to go.
看看我  真是白瞎了我有两条胳膊
Look at me. Look at me. I'm a waste of two arms.
我连水果塔都做不出来
I can't make a tart!
水果塔做得怎么样了
How's the tart coming?
阿憨  这里不安全  快走
Han, you're not safe. Leave.
你连塔皮还没有做出来
You haven't even finished the shell?
这可是最简单的部分啊
That's the easiest part!
阿憨  这是你的脸
Han, this is your face.
好吧  我还是走吧
Well, I should get going.
真不知道她能把坏脾气上升到暴力事件
I didn't know she could take bitch to the next level.
我彻底完了
I am so screwed!
终于出现一种情况  不能靠我的大胸过关了
I finally found a situation my boobs can't get me out of!
麦克斯  我对你超级有信心
Hey, Max. Now, I have all the faith in the world in you.
但这是我从便利店买来的水果塔
But here's a tart from Stop 'n Shop
以备明天不时之需
in case you wanted to hand this one in.
不行  厄尔  麦克斯从不骗人
No, Earl. Max is not a cheater.
谁说的
Since when?
她要靠自己做出水果塔
She is going to make her own tart.
你  出去
You, out.
我肯定做不出塔皮
I am never gonna make this shell.
我连放到盘里都放不对
I can't even get it in the pan right.
麦克斯  你放对了
Max, that looks right.
天啊  我放对了
Oh, my god! I got it in the pan right!
-我可以做到  -你做到了  我就知道
- I can do this! - You did it! I knew it!
我帮了你  我们是好闺蜜
I helped you. We're besties.
-这里不安全  快走  -遵命
- You're not safe. Leave. - Okay.
告诉你  麦克斯  我吃过这么多水果塔[浪女]
I'm telling you, Max, I've tasted a lot of tarts,
你的最好吃
and yours is delicious.
你不是第一个这么说的人
You are not the first man to tell me that.
第一个这么说的人  现在在蹲牢子呢
The first man to tell me that is in jail.
他来了
Here he comes.
快看  他来了
Look at him. Here he comes.
下午好  女士们
Afternoon, ladies.
芝士火锅[法语]  艾菲尔铁塔
Bien fondue, Eiffel tower.
好的
Okay.
感谢你们的到来  可以开始试吃了吗
Thank you for coming. Shall we begin the tasting?
真令人兴奋  对吧
This is exciting, huh?
勒紧你的裤子
Keep it in your pants.
这是水果塔
And now for the tart.
这是麦克斯第一次做
It's Max's first ever.
我之前吃了一小块
I ate a slice earlier and it was like
尝起来宛若天堂啊
having a little piece of heaven.
快给我闭嘴
Don't do anything you're doing.
塔皮薄  里馅滑
It's flaky, creamy...
第一次就能做成这样  我很惊讶
For a first attempt, I am very impressed.
别惊讶  我不过做了个水果塔
Don't be. I made a tart.
又不是治愈了疱疹
It's not like I cured herpes
或是发明了能立刻冷冻苏打水的逆向微波炉
or invented a reverse microwave to instantly chill sodas.
好的  麦克斯
Okay, Max.
我和其他教员商量一下
I will talk it over with my faculty
你们回去等通知吧
and we will let you know.
你也等我通知吧
I'll let you know.
成功啦
Nailed that.
麦克斯
Max!
别偷我的东西了  你已经有清洁工了
Stop stealing my things! You got a cleaning lady!
放心  我是来还东西的
Relax. I am returning what I took.
这是你的盘子
Here's your plates.
这是你的银行卡  我从你钱包拿的
Oh, and here's your ATM card. I lifted it from your wallet.
对了  这是你的钱包
Oh, and here's your wallet.
里面不是有四十块吗
There was $40 in here.
那是以前的事了
There sure was.
至少把我丝芙兰的礼品卡还给我吧
At least give me back my gift card from Sephora.
卡洛琳  阿憨想要回他丝芙兰的礼品卡
Caroline, Han wants his Sephora gift card back.
要不回来了  全用在我脸上了
Oh, that's not happening. It's already on my face.
麦克斯  烘焙学校寄来的信
Max, look, it's from the pastry school.
厕所里有很多人在讨论我做的辣椒啊
Lot of people talking about my chili in that bathroom.
奥列格过来  阿憨和厄尔待在原地
Oleg, come here. Han, Earl, stay.
你们都要感谢我
You guys are about to owe me big.
因为我要让你们见证一件极其罕见的事
I am gonna let you witness something extremely rare.
比看见大脚怪  UFO还有阿憨的小鸡鸡还罕见哦
More rare than a sighting of bigfoot or a UFO or Han's penis.
你不让我走  是为了让我听这句话吗
You held me here so I could hear that?
各位观众  全世界最罕见的事情
Behold, the rarest sight of them all.
你们即将看见有好事要发生在我身上
You are about to see something good actually happen to me.
注意听啦
Listen to this.
"亲爱的布莱克小姐  在对众多申请者
"Dear Ms. Black, after careful consideration
进行深思熟虑之后
of our large pool of applicants,
我们抱歉地通知你"
we regret to inform you..."
我猜我没被录取
Oh, I guess I didn't get in.
回头想想  我们当初应该坚持
Looking back, we probably should have insisted
让她自己看那封信就好
she read that to herself first.
我知道她没被录取是因为她的姓
I know why she didn't get in. Her name.
他们一看见"布莱克[黑]"这个词  就把申请表扔一边了
They saw the word "Black" and stopped reading.
这就是为什么我没被法学院录取
That's why I didn't get into law school.
当然我也懒得申请
I also didn't apply.
这太糟糕了  我去看看她还好吗
This is terrible. I'm gonna go see if she's okay.
那只法国青蛙以为自己是谁啊
Who does that French frog think he is?
他觉得在品尝完我的水果塔后
He thinks he can have the time of his life tasting my tart
就可以拍拍屁股走人吗
and then never see me again?
他的学校不录取我
He won't let me into his school?
我不允许别人拒绝我
Well, I won't take no for an answer.
我现在就杀过去
I am going down there right now
告诉他我的真实想法
and giving him a piece of my mind.
气死我了
I am storming out.
我又死回来了
And I am storming back in.
天黑了  学校不开门
It is dark outside. That school's not open.
喂  就是你
Hey, you.
水果塔混球  我有话跟你说
Tart tease, we need a word.
你说你喜欢我的水果塔  然后抱歉地通知我
You love my pastries and then regret to inform me
我不够格念你的学校
I'm not good enough for your school?
我抱歉地通知你  我绝对够格
Well, I regret to inform you that I am good enough
我想知道你不录取我的原因
and I want to know why you won't let me in here.
你的声音会触发我的焦虑症
Okay, uh, your voice is an anxiety trigger for me.
现在这状况不适合我  我要离开这里
I'm going to have to remove myself from the situation
去走廊坐着
and go sit in the hallway.
你能陪我去吗  你的存在能安抚人心
Can you come with me? You have a very calming presence.
谢谢  很少有人会这么觉得
Thank you. So few people think that about me.
但我应该陪着麦克斯
But I should stay with Max.
去吧  我能处理好  你可以带她走
No, I got this handled. You can have her.
这是你最后一次把我扔给别人
This is the last time you give me to someone.
麦克斯  你的水果塔做得很棒
Max, your tart was excellent.
但问题在于你的态度
The problem was your attitude.
你对这个学校没表现出半点热忱
You showed no passion of wanting to be in this school.
这就是你没被录取的原因
And that is why you didn't get in.
因为你看上去并不想来这
It seemed like you didn't want it.
不  我对什么事都是这态度
No, no, no, that's just my attitude.
我表现得我不喜欢任何事物
I act like I don't want anything
是因为我从来没得到过我想要的
because I never got anything I wanted.
但我的确很想来这个学校
But I do want to go to this school
超越我以前所有热忱
more than I've ever wanted anything.
这是我的幻想  也是我的梦想
It's my fantasy and my dream,
拜托不要再让我继续说这些恶心的词了
and please stop making me use these horrible, horrible words!
求求你  录取我吧
Just let me in, okay?
好吧
Okay.
-等等  真的吗  -真的
- Wait, for real? - Yes.
我只想看看你的热忱是不是跟你的水果塔一样棒
I needed to see if your passion was as good as your pastry
而你已经表现给我看了
and you just showed me it was.
非常高兴你加入我们  大厨
I'm thrilled to have you on board, chef.
谢谢  主厨
Thanks, chef.
碧碧恐慌症发作  她说要抱她的柠檬
Bebe is having a panic attack and needs to hold her lemon.
有人见过她的柠檬吗
Has anyone seen her lemon?
卡洛琳  他录取我了  我要上烘焙学校啦
Caroline, he let me in. I'm going to pastry school.
从现在开始  人人都得叫我"大厨"
Everybody has to call me "Chef" now!
你成功了  大厨
You did it, chef!
你被宣传册上的烘焙学校录取了
You're going to the pastry school from the brochure!
你是不是该高兴我看了你的黄书啊
Aren't you glad I looked at your porn?
我们是室友  都是单身  很惊喜吧
We're roommates. Both single. Quelle surprise.
麦克斯  只要把表填了
So Max, once you fill out these,
你就算正式人学了
you will be officially enrolled.
当然你还得先交学费
And of course we will need your tuition check.
三千块嘛  这对我们来说是一大笔钱
Yup. $3,000. It's a lot for us.
但我们可以削减开支  厕纸省着用好了
But if we make some cutbacks, 1/2-ply toilet paper.
开什么玩笑  厕纸和餐巾纸都不要了
Who am I kidding? No toilet paper, diner napkins.
不  学费是两万四
No, tuition is 24,000.
但宣传册上是写一年三千啊
But the brochure said $3,000 a year.
你看错了  是一课时三千
You misread it. It's $3,000 a unit.
一年有八个课时呢  一共是两万四
There is eight units per year. 24,000.
学费要两万四
It costs $24,000?
这我们可付不起
We can't pay that.
天啊  我再也不能来这里了
Oh, my god, now I'm never gonna be able to come here
而我刚才却承认了我很想来
and I just admitted I wanted to!
我收回我刚说的话  我什么也不想要
I take back everything I ever said about wanting anything.
麦克斯  你不能就这么一走了之
Max, you can't just storm out.
你妹才一走了之
Your face can't just storm out!
为了让她上学  我愿意做一切事情
Look, I will do anything for that girl to go to this school.
我可以在办公室帮忙  以换取学费
In exchange for tuition, I could work in the office.
碧碧显然需要人来帮她解除压力
Bebe clearly needs someone to help take the pressure off
我是沃顿毕业  而且精神稳定
And who better than a mentally stable
没有比我更合适的人选了
Wharton graduate like myself?
但我什么都愿意干
But I'll do anything.
甚至连洗地板都行
I'll even wash your floors, okay?
虽然我觉得肯定有比这更好的活
Although I'm sure there's something better than that.
但如果你需要我洗地板
But if you need me to wash the floors,
我就洗地板
I will wash the floors.
虽然我更想做其他工作
Really would prefer to do anything else,
但我还是会做  因为为了她
but I'll do it, 'cause I'll do anything
我什么都愿意做
to get her into this school.
拜托不要让我洗地板
Please no floors.
好吧  我和其他员工商量一下
Okay, I will talk it over with my staff
你回去等通知吧
and I will let you know.
不  不行
Oh, no, no.
我知道你那句
I've seen what happens
"回去等通知"的后果
when you give people the "I'll let you know."
我哪儿不去  直到你当面告诉我
I'm not going anywhere until you let me know to my face.
用你那张帅气迷人的脸蛋告诉我
With your face. Your beautiful, beautiful face.